dunzo.net 2016-03-15

# 

#### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies of Voyager Media, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company ("we", "our" or "Dunzo") on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on www.dunzo.net ("Site") and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively, "Services"). As a result of your visitation to the Site, we receive information about you either related to means of electronic identification, such as your IP address or cookies, as well as information that you voluntarily submit to the website (collectively "Submitted Information"). This information enables Dunzo to personalize, improve, and continue to operate the Services. 

#### Third Party Uses of Submitted Information

We may also receive Submitted Information from third party organizations or individuals. By your use of the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, display, disclosure, and other uses of your information to third party individuals or organizations. However, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications that you elect to access through the Service, or to any individuals that we do not manage or employ. We collect the following types of information from our users. 

#### IP Address Information and Cookies

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address and cookies ("Identifying Information"). This Identifying Information is used for several purposes such as determining how frequently you and other individuals visit the Site, protecting the Site from malicious activity, and collecting data related to your interaction with the Services. Through the collection of this Identifying Information, Dunzo can more efficiently design its Services to provide you with content that represents what you want to see and to improve your experience with the Site. 

#### Advertising

To support and enhance the Services, we may provide advertisements, as well as allow third parties advertisements on our Site. These advertisements may be targeted and or may come from third party advertisement companies. When your web browser requests these advertisements from the third party advertisement company's servers, these companies can view, edit, or send you their own cookies, just as if you had clicked on a website link directly from their site. By using Dunzo's services, you consent to any cookies being placed onto your web browser either by Dunzo, or by any third party advertisement company. 

#### How we Collect and Use Non-Personally Identifying Information

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect data when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

#### California Residents

In California, you are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal information we share with any third parties for marketing purposes, as provided for in California Civil Code sections 1798.83 and 1798.84. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this information, please submit a written request to the following: support@voyagermedianetwork.com. 

#### User Comments

Dunzo permits you to provide your own content to the Site, including written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained and displayed by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. By your use of the Site, you understand that you may also display your comments onto third party websites of which you maintain an account, such as on Facebook or Twitter. Dunzo does not control any information that you simultaneously display on third party websites through the use of Dunzo's Services. Dunzo encourages you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of any third party websites, which may also display information posted through Dunzo. Effective Date: 04-02-2014 If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or want to contact us, please send an email to support@voyagermedianetwork.com
